Professional profile:

Finishing my degree in Information and Communication Technologies at KTH, bearing four languages in my head, equipped with competent programming skills and full of enthusiasm for getting new opportunities to push me into my future career in IT.

Education:

2020-2023 KTH

• Organizational skills, communication, paperwork, mathematical reasoning, programming languages, intensive reading, browsing/searching, and asking for help.

2008-2020: El Redín (Pamplona, Spain)

• 9.55 / 10 grade on average in the four last years of school.

Core skills:

- Professional-IT competence
- AGILE & SCRUM
- Active in volunteering
- Polyglot
- Tutoring experience

Career summary:

2022-2023 Academic year, Sophiahemmet: IT-Support:

Solving IT-related doubts to students and managing database information.

• Microsoft Active Directory

2020-2022 Academic year, Living For Others: Web-page administrator:

Web-page administrator, together with regular presence in charity activities.

• WordPress, Google suite, MS-suite.

2022 Spring, KTH & DTR1: Front-end programming

Group project programming together with DTR1 that consisted in building a large-scale electrical network mapping web service.

React, JavaScript, CSS, Git, SLACK, SCRUM methodology and AGILE development.

2021 Winter, KTH: Application-development project

Full process from market research to coding and testing stages. The project was achieved within the stipulated time with good grade result.

• Firebase, Vue-JS, React, CSS.

2021 Spring, KTH & KTHAIS: IT support team

Full stack development using Pyhton's Django along with a strong group of students collaborating together to carry the association into more active participation in KTH.

• Python, SLACK, Git

2020 Winter, KTH: C programming project

Group project where we needed to dive into the programming device's documentation in order to develop a game on a UNO32-board.

• C, MIPS assembly language, Git.